[
    {
        "Question": "includes",
        "Answer": "contains",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "incite",
        "Answer": "stimulate",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "inconclusive",
        "Answer": "not decisive",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "incorporated",
        "Answer": "become part of",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "incredible",
        "Answer": "unbelievable",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "indefinitely",
        "Answer": "without limit",
        "Options": "endlessly"
    },
    {
        "Question": "indefinite period",
        "Answer": "whose end has not been determined",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "indicative of",
        "Answer": "suggesting",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "indigenous",
        "Answer": "native",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "indiscriminate",
        "Answer": "random",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "indispensable",
        "Answer": "essential",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "induces",
        "Answer": "brings about/ stimulate",
        "Options": "cause the formation of"
    },
    {
        "Question": "in essence",
        "Answer": "basically",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "inevitable",
        "Answer": "certain/ necessary",
        "Options": "unavoidable"
    },
    {
        "Question": "inflating",
        "Answer": "enlarging",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "infrequent",
        "Answer": "uncommon",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "ingenious",
        "Answer": "inventive",
        "Options": "clever"
    },
    {
        "Question": "ingenuity",
        "Answer": "cleverness",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "ingested",
        "Answer": "eaten",
        "Options": "swallowed"
    },
    {
        "Question": "inherent",
        "Answer": "built-in",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "inhibit",
        "Answer": "restrict/ restrain",
        "Options": "slow down"
    },
    {
        "Question": "inhospitable",
        "Answer": "not suitable",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "initiate",
        "Answer": "begin/ start",
        "Options": "first"
    },
    {
        "Question": "innovation",
        "Answer": "new development",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "innumerable",
        "Answer": "countless",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "insights into",
        "Answer": "an understanding of",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "insisting",
        "Answer": "stating forcefully",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "installed",
        "Answer": "put in place",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "instigate",
        "Answer": "caused",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "instructive",
        "Answer": "informative",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "intact",
        "Answer": "undamaged",
        "Options": "whole"
    },
    {
        "Question": "integral",
        "Answer": "essential",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "intergrated",
        "Answer": "combined",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "interlocked",
        "Answer": "linked",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "interplay",
        "Answer": "interaction",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "intense",
        "Answer": "extreme",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "intensive",
        "Answer": "strong",
        "Options": "extreme"
    },
    {
        "Question": "intervals",
        "Answer": "periods",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "intercourse",
        "Answer": "exchange",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "intermittently",
        "Answer": "periodicaly",
        "Options": "regularly"
    },
    {
        "Question": "interpreted",
        "Answer": "understood",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "in the same breath",
        "Answer": "immediately",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "intricate",
        "Answer": "complex",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "intrinsically",
        "Answer": "fundamentally",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "inventive",
        "Answer": "creative",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "involved",
        "Answer": "complicated",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "invoked",
        "Answer": "called upon",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "irreversible",
        "Answer": "permanent",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "isolated",
        "Answer": "widely separated",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "is usually accompanied by",
        "Answer": "usually occurs together with",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "jointly",
        "Answer": "together",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "just",
        "Answer": "fair",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "justify",
        "Answer": "provide a rational basis for",
        "Options": "support"
    },
    {
        "Question": "keenly",
        "Answer": "deeply",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "kept in check",
        "Answer": "prevented",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "kept pace with",
        "Answer": "matched the increase in",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "key",
        "Answer": "essential",
        "Options": "important/ crucial"
    },
    {
        "Question": "lamented",
        "Answer": "complained about",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "largely renounces",
        "Answer": "generally rejects",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "lasted",
        "Answer": "endured",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "launched",
        "Answer": "started",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "lavishly",
        "Answer": "richly",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "leftover",
        "Answer": "remaining",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "legendary",
        "Answer": "famous",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "legible",
        "Answer": "recognizable",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "legitimately",
        "Answer": "officially",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "likewise",
        "Answer": "similarly",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "little",
        "Answer": "short of",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "location",
        "Answer": "place",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "lodge",
        "Answer": "embed",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "logical",
        "Answer": "reasonable",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "luminous",
        "Answer": "bright",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "lure",
        "Answer": "attract",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "magnify",
        "Answer": "increase",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "maintain",
        "Answer": "claim",
        "Options": "keep/ preserve"
    },
    {
        "Question": "managed",
        "Answer": "were able",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "mandated",
        "Answer": "required",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "manipulated",
        "Answer": "skillfully used",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "manifestations",
        "Answer": "expressions",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "marginally",
        "Answer": "slightly",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "margins",
        "Answer": "edges",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "marked",
        "Answer": "considerable",
        "Options": "noticeable"
    },
    {
        "Question": "massive",
        "Answer": "very large/ enormous",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "match",
        "Answer": "equal",
        "Options": "agree with"
    },
    {
        "Question": "meager",
        "Answer": "very low",
        "Options": "thin"
    },
    {
        "Question": "mechanisms",
        "Answer": "parts",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "mechanism for",
        "Answer": "means of",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "mechanisms of natural selection",
        "Answer": "ways natural selection works",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "mere",
        "Answer": "only",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "merge",
        "Answer": "combine",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "miniature",
        "Answer": "small",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "minute",
        "Answer": "tiny",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "modest",
        "Answer": "relatively small",
        "Options": "moderate"
    },
    {
        "Question": "modify",
        "Answer": "change",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "momentous",
        "Answer": "very important",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "monumental",
        "Answer": "enormous",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "moral",
        "Answer": "lesson",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "mortality",
        "Answer": "death",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "mundane",
        "Answer": "ordinary",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "mutual",
        "Answer": "shared",
        "Options": ""
    }
]